I'll go on Fox just like I'll go on CNN or MSNBC
if the message is right. And it always surprises
me at um how many people will unfriend me on
social media if I've gone on Fox. It's It's
nuts. It's like why why why do you put yourself in
a corner where you're only going to associate with
the people who agree with you on all the issues?
That doesn't make any sense to me. And you know
what? Let me tell you, if I So, I am single and
um and I'm I'm looking. So, I'm on these apps like
so many other people are and I meet this woman and
she is absolutely stunning. And not just stunning,
smart. She has a master's degree in archaeology
and she did a dig in Greece and a dig in in
Israel and she's in a very senior position
um in government at at at a deputy assistant
secretary position. Right? So we start texting,
we start calling and I said, "Listen, I I want
to be transparent and upfront. um you should
know a little bit about me. And she said, "Oh,
I know who you are, Mr. Kiryaku." I had never used
my last name, but she said, "I know who you are,
Mr. Kuryaku." I said, "Okay, great. Well, if
it's okay with you, then it's great with me.
Can't wait to go out. We go out to dinner. Have
a fantastic time." I ask her out a second time.
We go out the second time. Fantastic time. And
then I say to her, "Hey, there's this little
town outside Washington called uh Shepherd's Town,
West Virginia." I said, "It's a it's got like art
galleries and boutiques and bars and restaurants.
Let's go on Saturday and we'll walk around town.
We'll have lunch and, you know, hang out." She
said, "Great." I pick her up 10:00 on a Saturday
morning. As soon as she gets in my car, my my
car, I can tell something's wrong. So, I said,
"Are you okay? What's wrong?" "Nothing. Nothing."
She goes, "Nothing. Everything's fine." I said,
"Well, clearly something's bothering you. what
is it? And she says, "Well, I have doubts about
your progressive credentials." And I said, "Excuse
me?" I said, "I went to prison for my progressive
credentials." And then she says, "I saw a YouTube
video of you last night in which you quoted Ronald
Reagan." And I said, "All right, I know what quote
you're talking about." I said, "Ronald Reagan
was right when he said that government is the
problem. It's not the solution to the problem."
But the rest of that quote was, I said, "Even a
broken clock is right twice a day." And she says,
"I just need to process this. I need to think
about it." it. I'm like, "Okay, whatever."
We go to Shepherd's Town, have a nice time, but
she's kind of cool for the for the day. Finally,
around 3:00, it starts to rain, and it's raining
kind of heavily. So, I said, "Look, why don't we
just get in the car? We'll go back to DC." So,
we get in the car, and I don't like to sit on my
phone when I'm in the car. So, I take my phone out
of my back pocket. I put it in the cup holder and
we're driving and I get a text message. It goes.
So I I look and I thought, "Fuck." It was a text
message from Tucker Carlson and it said, it said,
"Hey buddy, haven't heard from you in a while.
Let me know if you're free for a beer." So, I kind
of I give her the side eye like this just to see,
you know, has she noticed? And she's like, "Who
is that, John?" Yeah. Looking at the text message.
So, I pretend I didn't notice. And then she goes,
"Do you know Tucker Carlson?" And I said, "Yes,
and he's a lovely guy. You don't have to agree
with him. I disagree with him on 95% of the
issues, but he's a nice guy." and she says, "Take
me home right now and don't ever call me again."
So, I did. But that's Washington in 2024. That's
Isn't that on par with your tagline from your
show? The red team, blue team. Everybody needs to
have this tribalistic. It's either red team, blue
team. No in between, no nuance. That's it. Can you
imagine just as recently as the 1990s, Republican
and Democratic members of Congress used to live
together in group houses on Capitol Hill, play
poker together on Fridays, go to church together
on Sundays. Now they would just assume kill each
other. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That's the level of the
discourse. But the Democratic Party is is hor in
horrible horrible shape. Terrible. The neoliberal,
they have lost their minds. And it's all led by
this old mummified uh guy walking around who's
barely sentient. He doesn't know where he is
half the time. Can't find a chair to sit down
in wandering off the stage. Um and and then
beyond that just um imperialist genocidal kind of
foreign policy. Even Kissinger said, "I see no aim
in the current United States foreign policy." Even
Kissinger was like, "You guys are doing it wrong."
You know, it's funny that you say that because
just last night I had a similar conversation
in which I told a friend of mine that as much of
a genocidal maniac as Kissinger was, he at least
had goals in foreign policy. You know, you can
disagree about what he did in Chile and Cyprus and
Vietnam and a dozen other places around the world,
but you knew what his policy was. you knew what
the goal was and Raal Polyik was real. It was only
because of Kissinger that Nixon went to China. It
was only because of Kissinger that that Nixon and
Brev were able to negotiate dant. And you're right
there there's no discernable policy from this
administration or the last one for that matter
and even the one before Barack Obama. I mean, it
was it was just kind of a standard run-of-the-mill
neoliberal warloving, you know, lead from behind
and still pretend to be the leader kind of kind
of traditional policy. Nothing bold, nothing
special, certainly nothing advocating peace in
any way. No. And I mean Kissinger didn't advocate
for peace necessarily, but at the same time the
the the end result was at least and not that
I'm for imperialism at all, but at least the
end goal was to strengthen the United States.
But in in the case of everything since Bush,
it's been actually to create more enemies abroad.
That's right. It seems or maybe that's uh on
accident or whatever, but yeah, it just seems like
there's not anything clear now. You we're steeped
in Ukraine and everything like this. Mhm. and and
look at the drone program just as one example. Um,
you know, so many of us thought this was a fluke
of the George W. Bush administration and it
wasn't. The drone program is probably the single
biggest the single most important recruiting tool
for terrorist groups that exists. I can't tell you
how many al-Qaeda fighters I captured or helped to
capture who told exactly the same thing that they
had no beef with the American government until
our drones killed their dads, their brothers,
their uncles, their imam, blew up the village,
blew up the school, blew up the hospital, and then
they were compelled to take up arms against us.
Well, you know, in George W. Bush's last month as
president, he killed 24 people with drones. And in
Barack Obama's last month as president, he killed
more than 400 people with drones. So, you know,
what kind of policy is that? It's a policy of
failure. And what do we get out of it? I mean,
what you can say that the war on terror was some
vague idea about going and getting vengeance in
all these people, but were we trying to get oil
out of Iraq or what? Just stealing the resource.
Was that that's really the goal, I guess. Um, so
I did I did want to ask you about Go ahead. Yeah.
Uh I w I did want to ask you because you know
we got right now there's a conflict in Georgia
uh that seems to be instigated without
any credibility. We don't know for sure
but it seems like the CIA is behind this color
revolution that's going on in Georgia. Ukraine
is obviously being backed by the United
States pretty heavily. Uh, and Noni. Now,
Noni was an interesting character and I wanted to
get your take on it because he went to Yale and
and you were you were actually the one who was
recruited from a university. He went to Yale,
which is like one of the places that they are
known to have CIA recruitment programs. What's
your take on Noni? What's your take on Georgia
and these kind of things? Well, let's talk about
Georgia first. I'm fascinated by what's happening
in Georgia. Um, but I think that the bottom line
there is actually quite clear. Um, the bottom line
is that our policy, whether it's stated or not,
is to create as many problems for the Russians,
especially on their borders, as we possibly can.
So, you know, we're we're pumping tens of billions
of dollars into Ukraine. Uh, we're not going to
stop. You know, that joke that we'll fight to
the last Ukrainian, that's actually not a joke.
It's the policy, right? We will fight to the
last Ukrainian. Um, so we've got that. We've
got the policy of of encirclement. You know, the
the Baltic countries are all in NATO. Poland's in
NATO. Ukraine is de facto NATO. And um and why not
stir up trouble in Georgia, you know, whether it's
over this stupid uh foreign agent registration
copycat law or just stirring, you know,
poking the hornets's nest to to draw the Russians
in. I'm surprised we're only doing it in Georgia.
I'm surprised we're not also doing it in Armenia.
You know, the Russians have tried hard to to walk
a tight rope between the Armenians and the and the
Azeris. We don't give a [__] about the Azeris.
I'm surprised we haven't jumped in with both feet
on the side of the Armenians. If only I mean, it's
not cuz we even care about the Armenians. If only
to upset the Russians. So, to me, that's that's
sort of the the easy issue. Now, Nani, I don't
have the foggiest idea if Noni was working for the
CIA or the FBI or if they even ever approached
him. I have no idea, but I can speculate.